{
  "decks": [
    {
      "initialDeckState": {
        "name": "",
        "description": ""
      },
      "name": "oops",
      "description": "some text",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "initialDeckState": {
        "name": "",
        "description": ""
      },
      "name": "Oopsie",
      "description": "Poopsie",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "initialDeckState": {
        "name": "",
        "description": ""
      },
      "name": "All of the Cats",
      "description": "Cat quiz",
      "id": 6
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Hello",
      "back": "Bye",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "aint",
      "back": "enough",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "what about",
      "back": "now",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "hello",
      "back": "please work",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "hello",
      "back": "bye",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "yay",
      "back": "boo",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "foo",
      "back": "bar",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "Jago",
      "back": "hood cat",
      "deckId": 6,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "Everglow",
      "back": "Ever Hoe",
      "deckId": 6,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "Apollo",
      "back": "App Olo",
      "deckId": 6,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "Aeris",
      "back": "Titty Baby",
      "deckId": 6,
      "id": 17
    }
  ]
}